A Guide to the Papers of the President of the University of Virginia, Office Administrative Files, 1969-1970
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
- Series I: General Files, 1969-1970
  - Student Council report: Dream Deferred: U.Va. and Equal Opportunity, 1967-19701969-1970 (Box 57)
  - Student Council 1969-1970 (Box 57)
  - Student Health Department 1969-1970 (Box 58)
  - Student Legal Forum 1969-1970 (Box 58)
  - Student Placement 1969-1970 (Box 58)
  - Summer Session 1969 1969-1970 (Box 58)
  - "T" Miscellaneous 1969-1970 (Box 58)
  - Tayloe Murphy Institute (see also special file # 4137-AC) 1969-1970 (Box 59)
  - Toms, Peter C. 1969-1970 (Box 59)
  - Traffic Control 1969-1970 (Box 59)
  - Tuitions and Fees 1969-1970 (Box 59)
  - "U" Miscellaneous 1969-1970 (Box 59)
  - United Givers Fund 1969-1970 (Box 59)
  - UKESCO 1969-1970 (Box 59)
  - U. S. Department of Agriculture 1969-1970 (Box 60)
  - U. S. Department of Defense 1969-1970 (Box 60)
  - U. S. Department of Health, Education, and Welfare 1969-1970 (Box 60)
  - U. S. Department of State 1969-1970 (Box 60)
  - U. S. Naval Academy 1969-1970 (Box 60)
  - University Center in Virginia 1969-1970 (Box 60)
  - University Hall (see also Field House Committee) 1969-1970 (Box 60)
  - University Houses - General 1969-1970 (Box 60)
  - University Press of Virginia 1969-1970 (Box 60)
  - University Printing Office 1969-1970 (Box 60)
  - Upward Bound 1969-1970 (Box 60)
  - University Relations 1969-1970 (Box 60)
  - Universities Research Association 1969-1970 (Box 60)
  - University Union (see also Newcomb Hall) 1969-1970 (Box 60)
  - "V" Miscellaneous 1969-1970 (Box 61)
  - Virginia Academy of Science 1969-1970 (Box 61)
  - Virginia Advisory Legislative Council 1969-1970 (Box 61)
  - Virginia Commission on Higher Education Facilities 1969-1970 (Box 61)
  - Virginia Education Association 1969-1970 (Box 61)
  - Virginia Historical Society 1969-1970 (Box 61)
  - Virginia Highway Research Council: 22nd Annual Report, June 19701969-1970 (Box 61)
  - Vietnam Moratorium 1969-1970 (Box 62)
  - Virginia Quarterly Review 1969-1970 (Box 62)
  - Virginia State Chamber of Commerce 1969-1970 (Box 62)
  - Virginia Student Aid Foundation 1969-1970 (Box 62)
  - Virginia Weekly 1969-1970 (Box 62)
  - Visitors - General 1969-1970 (Box 62)
  - Visitors - Board Committee - Buildings and Grounds 1969-1970 (Box 62)
  - Visitors - Board Committee - Educational Policy 1969-1970 (Box 63)
  - Visitors - Board Committee - Executive 1969-1970 (Box 63)
  - Visitors - Board Committee - Finance 1969-1970 (Box 63)
  - Visitors - Board Committee - Medical 1969-1970 (Box 63)
  - Visitors - Board Committee - Mary Washington College 1969-1970 (Box 63)
  - Visitors - Board Committee - Student Affairs and Athletics 1969-1970 (Box 63)
  - Visitors - Minutes, 3 October 1969 1969-1970 (Box 65)
  - Visitors - Docket, 6 December 1969 1969-1970 (Box 65)
  - Visitors - Minutes, 6 December 1969 1969-1970 (Box 65)
  - Visitors - Docket, 7 February 1970 1969-1970 (Box 65)
  - Visitors - Minutes, 7 February 1970 1969-1970 (Box 65)
  - Visitors - Minutes, 9 March 1970 1969-1970 (Box 65)
  - Visitors - Docket, 11 April 1970 1969-1970 (Box 65)
  - Visitors - Minutes, 11 April 1970 1969-1970 (Box 65)
  - Visitors - Docket, 5 June 1970 1969-1970 (Box 65)
  - Visitors - Minutes, 5 June 1970 1969-1970 (Box 66)
  - "W - Wh" Miscellaneous 1969-1970 (Box 66)
  - "Wi - Wz" Miscellaneous 1969-1970 (Box 66)
  - Walpole Society 1969-1970 (Box 66)
  - Washington Center for Metropolitan Studies 1969-1970 (Box 66)
  - Water Pollution Control 1969-1970 (Box 66)
  - Women, Dean of 1969-1970 (Box 66)
  - "X - Y - Z" Miscellaneous 1969-1970 (Box 66)
- Series II: University Committees, 1969-1970
  - AD HOC - Summer Work-Study Preparatory Program 1969-1970 (Box 67)
  - AD HOC - Open Meeting with Visitors 1969-1970 (Box 67)
  - [File]- Pending for Committee Appointments 1969-1970 (Box 67)
  - [File]- Students Nominated by Student Council 1969-1970 (Box 67)
  - [File]- Administrative Committees 1969-1970 (Box 68)
  - Committee - Arboretum 1969-1970 (Box 68)
  - Committee - Admissions 1969-1970 (Box 68)
  - Committee - Algernon Sydney Sullivan Award 1969-1970 (Box 68)
  - Committee - Architectural Advisory Committee 1969-1970 (Box 68)
  - Committee - Athletic Advisory Committee 1969-1970 (Box 68)
  - Committee - Athletic Advisory Council 1969-1970 (Box 68)
  - Committee - Calendar of Events 1969-1970 (Box 68)
  - Committee - Calendar and Scheduling 1969-1970 (Box 68)
  - Committee - Catalogue 1969-1970 (Box 68)
  - Committee - Chapel 1969-1970 (Box 68)
  - Committee - Communications (folder empty) 1969-1970 (Box 68)
  - Committee - Computer-Science Center 1969-1970 (Box 68)
  - Committee - Community Colleges 1969-1970 (Box 68)
  - Committee - Danforth Fellowships 1969-1970 (Box 68)
  - Committee - Data Processing (folder empty) 1969-1970 (Box 68)
  - Committee - Extensions Activities 1969-1970 (Box 68)
  - Committee - Foreign Students 1969-1970 (Box 68)
  - Committee - Fraternities 1969-1970 (Box 68)
  - Committee - Fulbright Grants 1969-1970 (Box 68)
  - Committee - Graduate (folder empty) 1969-1970 (Box 68)
  - Committee - Graduate Awards and Recruiting (folder empty) 1969-1970 (Box 68)
  - Committee - Graphics (folder empty) 1969-1970 (Box 68)
  - Committee - Housing 1969-1970 (Box 68)
  - Committee - Institutional Analysis 1969-1970 (Box 69)
  - Committee - Lectures (Page-Barbour and Richard) 1969-1970 (Box 69)
  - Committee - Library 1969-1970 (Box 69)
  - Committee - Master Plan 1969-1970 (Box 69)
  - Committee - Names 1969-1970 (Box 69)
  - Committee - Placement 1969-1970 (Box 69)
  - Committee - Processions 1969-1970 (Box 69)
  - Committee - Public Occasions 1969-1970 (Box 69)
  - Committee - Publications 1969-1970 (Box 69)
  - Committee - RADIATION SAFETY 1969-1970 (Box 69)
  - Committee - Records (folder empty) 1969-1970 (Box 69)
  - Committee - Registration 1969-1970 (Box 69)
  - Committee - Research and Sponsored Programs 1969-1970 (Box 69)
  - Committee - Rhodes Scholarship 1969-1970 (Box 69)
  - Committee - ROTC Affairs 1969-1970 (Box 69)
  - Committee - Schedule of Events (folder empty) 1969-1970 (Box 69)
  - Committee - Scholarships and Fellowships, Grants... Employment Fellows. 1969-1970 (Box 69)
  - Committee - Security and General Safety 1969-1970 (Box 69)
  - Committee - Student Activities 1969-1970 (Box 69)
  - Committee - Summer Grants 1969-1970 (Box 69)
  - Committee - Summer Session 1969-1970 (Box 69)
  - Committee - Teacher Education (folder empty) 1969-1970 (Box 69)
  - Committee - Traffic Control 1969-1970 (Box 69)
  - Committee - University Colleges 1969-1970 (Box 69)
  - Committee - University Committee on Students 1969-1970 (Box 69)
  - Committee - University Environment 1969-1970 (Box 69)
  - Committee - University Union 1969-1970 (Box 69)
  - Committee - Virginia Status on University Students 1969-1970 (Box 69)